[{"question": " my god, get a room!", "answer": " i would get a room with this cake. i think i could show this cake a good time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " if you had to, what would you give up, food or sex?", "answer": "  sex!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  seriously, answer faster!", "answer": " oh, i'm sorry honey, you know, but when she said &quot;sex&quot; i wasn't thinking about &quot;sex with you&quot;!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  it's like a giant hug.", "answer": " ross, how about you. what would you give up, sex or food?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " food.", "answer": " ok, how about... uhm... sex or dinosaurs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh my god. it's like sophie's choice.", "answer": " oh god. what about you, joe? what would you give up, sex or food?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " uhm... oh... i don't know, it's too hard.", "answer": " no, you gotta pick one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " you gotta see these latest pictures of emma.", "answer": " oh, how cute!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " oh, she looks just like a little doll!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " oh, no, no. that is a doll.", "answer": " oh, thank god, 'cause that thing's really creepy!  look, there's chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " oh. who is the blonde, she's pretty.", "answer": " oh! he's having an affair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " he's not having an affair!", "answer": " you know, i'm always right about these things.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " no, you're not! last week you thought ross was trying to kill you!", "answer": " well, i'm sorry but it's hard to believe that anyone would tell a story that dull just to tell it!  see, there's something going on with them. look, he's getting into the car with her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " oh, that doesn't mean anything.", "answer": " oh yeah? well, let's see.  ok, duck down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  hello.", "answer": " oh, hi chandler. it's phoebe. uhm... i know that monica is working today so... ...i was wondering if you want to come to the movies with me and rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " oh, uhm... i have to work too. yeah, i'm stuck at the office all day.", "answer": "  oh, well, it's a shame that you-that you miss the movie 'cause we were gonna see, you know, either &quot;liar, liar&quot; or &quot;betrayal&quot;, or... &quot;an affair to remember&quot;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " those are all really old!", "answer": " ok, then maybe it'll be, uhm...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  &quot;dude, where's my car?&quot;", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " they're in a caaar...", "answer": "  okay, we-we'll talk to you later. okay, bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " geez!", "answer": " ok. quick. we gotta find a cab and follow them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " oh, yeah, ok. let me just grab my night vision goggles and my stun gun.", "answer": "  i got them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey! you smell like perfume and cigarettes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " i was in the car with nancy all day.", "answer": " nancy doesn&#8217;t smoke!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " well, at least the perfume is not mine, be thankful for that!", "answer": " so? what do you think of the house?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " it&#8217;s perfect. it&#8217;s everything we&#8217;ve been looking for.", "answer": " isn&#8217;t it? then what about the amazing wainscotting and the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " and the wiggle wharms and the zip zorps?  what were the things you said?", "answer": " don&#8217;t you love the huge yard?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " and the fireplace in the bedroom.", "answer": " and nancy said that it's really under price, because the guy lost his job and has to move in with his parents!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " this is bringing out a lovely color in you!", "answer": " so? do you think we should get it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " i don&#8217;t know. what do you think?", "answer": " i think we should.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i do too.", "answer": " this is huge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " how bad you wanna smoke, right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " i don&#8217;t know what you mean, giant talking cigarette! oh, by the way, phoebe called just as i was getting into nancy&#8217;s car, so if she asks you, i was at work all day.", "answer": " gotcha. when do we tell them about this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " we don&#8217;t. not until it's a hundred percent. i mean, why upset everybody over nothing.", "answer": " okay. right. oh my god that is gonna be so hard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " i just can&#8217;t see chandler cheating!", "answer": " i&#8217;m telling you guys, we followed them out to a house in westchester, the went in for like forty-five minutes and then they came out looking pretty happy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " chandler? forty-five minutes? well, something is not right. i just can&#8217;t believe he would do this to monica!", "answer": " i know, and with the baby coming?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " so, should we tell her?", "answer": " i don&#8217;t know. phoebe, if one of us saw mike with another woman would you want us to tell you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " why? who&#8217;d you seen him with?", "answer": " no one, i&#8217;m just saying if...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " tell me what you know!", "answer": "  i know nothing! mike&#8217;s a great guy, it was hypothetical!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " all right. . he is a good guy. you&#8217;re right, he wouldn&#8217;t cheat.", "answer": " believe me, if i did see with someone, there&#8217;s no way i...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh, look at her, so happy!", "answer": " if only there were a smaller one to clean this one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " hey, is uhm... is chandler here?", "answer": " no, he&#8217;s picking up dinner, why, what&#8217;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " well, look, whatever happens, we&#8217;re here for you and we love you.", "answer": " all right...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " we think chandler might be having an affair.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " phoebe and i saw chandler with a blonde woman today outside on the street and then we followed them to a house in westchester.", "answer": " they went in together. so sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " what?", "answer": "  monica, you understand what we are saying, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  you son of a bitch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " is it me, or have the greetings gone downhill around here?", "answer": "  phoebe and rachel saw you with nancy today and... em... they think you're having an affair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " who's nancy?", "answer": " what's going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  ok, alright, you guys, you'd better sit down, this is pretty big.", "answer": " yeah  i'm not having an affair. nancy is our realtor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i knew he couldn't be with a woman for 45 minutes!!", "answer": " why do you have a realtor?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " uhm, she has been showing us houses outside of the city.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " are you serious?", "answer": " when we found out that we're gonna get this baby, chandler and i started talking and we decided that we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " so you're gonna move?", "answer": " oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?!", "answer": " what is wrong with raising a kid in the city? i'm doing it, ross is doing it, sarah jessica parker is doing it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " and that's great for you guys, but we want a lawn and a swingset...", "answer": " ...and a street where our kids can ride their bikes and maybe an ice-cream truck can go by.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  so you wanna buy a house in the 50's?", "answer": " have you thought about what you would be giving up? you can't move out of the city, what if you want chinese food at 5am? or a fake rolex that breaks as soon as it rains or an asian hooker sent right to your door?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " you know what, if you wanna look for a house, that's okay.", "answer": " no, no, it's not, don't listen to him!  i'm gonna thump you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " actually, we already found a house we love.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " bet you wish i was having an affair now, huh? time lapse", "answer": " you put an offer on a house?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " wha..? again with the nature, what are you? beavers?", "answer": " i know this is really hard and we're really sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " is this because i come over here without knocking and eat your food?  because i can stop doing that,  i really, really think i can!", "answer": "  you know that's not the reason joe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " we think if you saw it, you'd understand. i mean you guys were there.  it is beautiful, isn't it?", "answer": " yeah it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " what the hell are you doin'?", "answer": " well, it is, all right? when we were out there today, all i kept thinking was: i can't believe chandler is screwing this woman, but man this would be a nice place to live!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " yeah, but so is this.", "answer": " yeah, i mean, if you moved there, you have to leave here. i mean, how can you leave this place?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  c'mon daddy, listen to me! all of my life, everyone has always told me, 'you're a shoe! you're a shoe, you're a shoe, you're a shoe!'. and today i just stopped and i said, 'what if i don't wanna be a shoe? what if i wanna be a- a purse, y'know? or a- or a hat! no, i don't want you to buy me a hat, i'm saying that i am a ha- it's a metaphor, daddy!", "answer": " you can see where he'd have trouble.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " well maybe i'll just stay here with monica.", "answer": " well, i guess we've established who's staying here with monica...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " that money is mine, green!", "answer": " you're fly is open, geller!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " you guys, you know what i just realized? 'joker' is 'poker' with a 'j.' coincidence?", "answer": " hey, that's...'joincidence' with a 'c'!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " hey, it&#8217;s your thanksgiving too, y'know, instead of watching football, you could help.", "answer": " we will.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " okay, rachel, you wanna put the marshmallows in concentric circles.", "answer": " no mon, you want to put them in concentric circles. i want to do this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  it's stuck!!!", "answer": "  easy. step. how did it get on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i put it on to scare chandler!", "answer": " oh my god! monica's gonna totally freak out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " it smells really bad in here.", "answer": " well, of course it smells really bad. you have your head inside a turkey's ass!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " hey, did you get the turkey bast-oh my god! oh my god!  who is that?", "answer": " it's joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i got it! how about, if we win, they have to get rid of the rooster?", "answer": " oooohh that&#8217;s interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " if you win, we give up the birds.", "answer": "  dah!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " but if we win, we get your apartment.", "answer": " oooooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " deal! time lapse", "answer": " what was monica&#8217;s nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " big fat goalie.", "answer": " correct. rachel claims this is her favorite movie&#8230;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " dangerous liaisons.", "answer": " correct. her actual favorite movie is...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " weekend at bernie&#8217;s.", "answer": " monica categorizes her towels. how many categories are there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " everyday use.", "answer": " fancy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " guest.", "answer": " fancy guest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " two seconds...", "answer": " uhh, 11!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  chandler was how old when he first touched a girl&#8217;s breast?", "answer": " 14?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " no, 19.", "answer": " thanks man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " joey had an imaginary childhood friend. his name was?", "answer": " maurice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " correct, his profession was?", "answer": " space cowboy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " ow...oh gosh!", "answer": " 10 seconds, you need this or you lose the game.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " it&#8217;s umm, it has something to do with transponding.", "answer": " oh-oh-oh, he&#8217;s a transponce&#8212;transpondster!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " y&#8217;know what, you are mean boys, who are just being mean!", "answer": " hey, don&#8217;t get mad at us! no one forced you to raise the stakes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " that is not true. she did! she forced me!", "answer": " hey, we would still be living here if hadn&#8217;t gotten the question wrong!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " well it stupid, unfair question!", "answer": " don&#8217;t blame the questions!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " chandler!!! chandler!!!  chandler, i saw what you were doing through the window! chandler, i saw what you were doing to my sister! now get out here!", "answer": "  wow! listen, we had a good run. you know, what was it? four? five months? i mean, that's more than most people have in a lifetime! so, good-bye, take care, bye-bye then!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " what the hell are doing?!!", "answer": "  hey, what's-what's going on?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " well, i think, i think ross knows about me and monica.", "answer": "  dude! he's right there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  i thought you were my best friend, this is my sister! my best friend and my sister! i-i cannot believe this!", "answer": " look, we're not just messing around! i love her. okay, i'm in love with her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " well, this is the last box of your clothes. i&#8217;m just gonna label it, &quot;what were you thinking?&quot;", "answer": " funny, because i was just gonna go across the hall and write that on chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " ok, you guys, i don&#8217;t mean to make things worse, but umm, i don&#8217;t want to live with rachel anymore. monica and rachel: what?!", "answer": " you&#8217;re just so mean to each other! and i don&#8217;t want to end up like that with rachel. i still like you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " well, phoebe that&#8217;s fine because i&#8217;m not moving.", "answer": " whoa-whoa-whoa, phoebe you gotta take her! y&#8217;know, i-i-i said some really bad stuff about her, but y&#8217;know rachel has some good qualities that make her a good roommate. she gets tons of catalogs and umm, she&#8217;ll fold down the pages of the things she thinks that i&#8217;d like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " what else?", "answer": " when i take a shower, she leaves me little notes on the mirror.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " yeah, i do. i-i do, do that.", "answer": " that&#8217;s nice. i like having things to read in the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " when i fall asleep on the couch after reading, she covers me over with a blanket.", "answer": " well y&#8217;know, i don&#8217;t want you to be cold.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " she really left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " no problem roomie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " can i ask you a question?", "answer": " sure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " little toast here. i know this isn't exactly the kind of thanksgiving that all of you all planned, but for me, this has been really great, you know, i think because it didn't involve divorce or projectile vomiting. anyway, i was just thinking, i mean, if you'd gone to vail, and if you guys'd been with your family, if you didn't have syphilis and stuff, we wouldn't be all together, you know? so i guess what i'm trying to say is that i'm very thankful that all of your thanksgivings sucked.", "answer": " that's so sweet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " and hey, here's to a lousy christmas.", "answer": " and a crappy new year.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " you can't move. you just... you just can't.", "answer": " rachel's right. this is where you guys belong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " yeah, you don't wanna live in westchester. that's like the worst of the chesters.", "answer": " you know, sometimes when i'm alone in my apartment, i look over here and you guys... are just having dinner or... watching tv or something, but... it makes me feel better. and now when i look over, who am i gonna see? the gottliebs, the yangs? they don't make me feel so good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " hello? it's nancy, they responded to our offer.", "answer": " and?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": "  okay, thanks...  they passed. they said they wouldn't go a penny under the asking price.", "answer": " we can't afford that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " well, there you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " i'm really sorry you guys.", "answer": " yeah. i'm sorry too. i'm even more sorry that that phone call didn't come before i told you about looking through the window.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " yeah, we're gonna let you be alone.", "answer": "  you're gonna be okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " yeah, we'll be okay.", "answer": " love you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " you know, i'm really sorry i wasn't more supportive before.", "answer": " that's okay, we understand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " i know there'll be other houses, but it's just so... i love that one so much.", "answer": " yeah... well, it's a good thing we got it then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " we got the house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " i just didn't want to tell you in front of them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " oh my god! my god! we've got the house !?", "answer": " we're getting the house.  we're getting the house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " and a baby...", "answer": " we're growing up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " we sure are.", "answer": " so who's gonna tell them?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": "  not it!", "answer": " not it! damn it! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " rachel, this is yours.", "answer": " aah! why? what are these for?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " you'll see.", "answer": " all right, everybody open them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " i love this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " seriously you guys, what's going on? what are these for?", "answer": " well, i didn't know how to tell you before, but... we got the house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}]